{
    "id": "06e348f85af343aa813120adc334954d",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "James is honest ..................... industrious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as well as",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "951ea98bdc94486abf1b25448dba4c96"
        },
        {
            "question": "He neither respects his aged parents ………………. helps them financially.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3684e53b2798420b96ffed0ea40cde53"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. did I reach the station than the train left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner",
                "As soon as",
                "Hardly when"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "239bc6fbe26e4a868c69b1c36627a365"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. love and respect my parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "so",
                "so much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1221500a42184e078b046acb0478d015"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know ………………….. I will be able to come or not.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "537e3def1b154de1a3d402455ec84263"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………. honest but also generous.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not only",
                "not",
                "only"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e99fee881e7848b7a39c5fbcc686593e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is so rich ..................... .. he doesn’t have to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "36f021d49a534333b0e2bec0dc83d095"
        },
        {
            "question": "Walk briskly ..................... you should miss the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lest",
                "unless",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "140d7e5e69714b53aa98815dbe346efa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had hardly solved one issue …………………. another one cropped up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "until",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1537b6f9b38d4880b20a6aed19db5b73"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the same woman ………………… came to my house yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6834f388aa1e4b86babc4a58b84a967f"
        }
    ]
}